Privacy Policy
==============

We, Privado Inc (“**Privado**” or “**we**” or “**us**”) are the owners of the website [www.privado.ai](http://www.privado.ai/) (the “**Website**”). We take your privacy seriously and are committed to safeguarding your personal information collected on this Website.  This privacy policy (“**Privacy Policy**”) sets forth how we collect, use and protect the personal information collected on the Website.  
  
PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY. BY CLICKING “I AGREE” OR BY CONTINUING TO USE THE WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MAY NOT PROVIDE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION ON THE WEBSITE.

IF YOU ARE ACCESSING THE WEBSITE ON BEHALF OF A THIRD PARTY, YOU REPRESENT THAT YOU HAVE THE AUTHORITY TO BIND SUCH THIRD-PARTY TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND, IN SUCH AN EVENT YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE SHALL REFER TO USE BY SUCH THIRD PARTY. IF YOU DO NOT HAVE SUCH AN AUTHORITY (TO PROVIDE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION OF A THIRD PARTY) OR DO NOT AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, THEN YOU SHOULD REFRAIN FROM USING THE WEBSITE.

This Privacy Policy is an electronic record in the form of an electronic contract being compliant and construed in accordance with the data protection laws of various jurisdiction such as Indian Information Technology (Reasonable Security Practices and Procedures and Sensitive Personal Data or Information) Rules, 2011 under Information Technology Act 2000 (“Privacy Rules”) that require publishing of privacy policy for collection, use, storage and transfer of sensitive personal data or information, The European Union (“EU”) general data protection laws (“the GDPR”), and applicable data protection laws of the United States of America.

‍  
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or your personal information, please contact us using the details provided in Section – ‘Contact us’ or you can email us at vaibhav@privado.in.

### 1\. Introduction

The Website showcases our services and product offerings (**“Offerings”**).  

### 2\. Information we collect about you

To get in touch with us through our Website, request for a demo of our Offerings, subscribe to our Offerings, connect with us through our chat bot, for login and account creation, opt for a free trail of our privac**y compliance platform, registering for newsletters you are required to provide us with your name, e-mail address, company name, address details, country, and contact number. For the sake** of brevity, the aforementioned information shall be referred to as “**Personal Information**”. We may also collect details related to the regulations in which you are interested, and information related to the content downloaded.

* **Analytics and Tracking tools**  
    **Google Analytics -** This Website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses cookies, text files that are stored on your computer and enable analysis of your use of the Website. The information generated by the cookies about your use of this website are usually transferred to a server of Google in the US and stored there. In case of activation of IP anonymization on this website your IP address from Google will be truncated within Member States of the European Union or other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases is the full IP address is transmitted to a Google server in the US and shortened there. You can refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser software. You can also prevent the data generated by the cookie and related to your use of the website to Google and the processing of these data by Google, by selecting the in the following link (https: // Download tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de) available browser plug-in and install it.
* Personal Information is collected from Google Analytics, cookies and similar tracking technologies.
* We may also receive Personal Information from third party service providers including online payment processing services, such as Stripe and other trusted third parties.

#### 2.1. Accuracy of information

Please make sure that any Personal Information you share with us is accurate and up to date information.

### 3\. **How we use your Personal Information**

We use the Personal Information for the following purposes:

* to provide you with information about our Offerings and/or our periodic newsletters;
* to respond to your requests;
* for creation or development of business intelligence or data analytics in relation to the Offerings provided by us (for this purpose we may share the Personal Information with certain software or tools available online);
* to manage our relationship with you;
* for internal record keeping;  
* to provide you with authorization to login and use your user account;
* to verify your identity;
* to maintain correct and up-to-date information about you;
* to identify you as a contracting party;
* to improve our Website;
* to enable automated handling of the subscriptions;
* to otherwise be able to provide the services to you and
* to comply with our legal or statutory obligations.

### 4\. **Cookies**

A cookie is a text file which is downloaded to your device when you visit a website. It can help identify your device whenever you visit that website. To make the best use of our Website or the mobile application, we would recommend you set your device or web browser to accept cookies. However, you can always choose to refuse our use of cookies. If you do so, you may not be able to use some portions of our Website or the mobile application. We can use cookies to:

* analyse how websites and apps perform and are used.
* give you content that matches your preferences.
* some cookies can help us to make sure your information is secure when using our services.
* ensure the website’s pages look consistent.

#### **4.1 What information we collect using cookies and other tracking technologies.**

We may collect information that does not directly reveal your specific identity or does not directly relate to you as an individual. We may automatically collect the following information when you use our Website:

* Your device, browsing actions and patterns collected automatically as you navigate through our Website.
* Usage details, time of requests, browser types, operating system, IP addresses and information collected through cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies.
* Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
* Information about your computer and internet connection, operating system and browser type.

### 5\. **Who do we disclose your data to?**.

We do not trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties any Personal Information. This does not include trusted third parties or subcontractors hired to provide services on our behalf. This includes those who act as data processors on our behalf, acting strictly under contract and in accordance with Article 28 GDPR. With your confidentiality and protection in mind, we will always strive to protect your data when dealing with third-party vendors and other data processors. As permitted by law, we may share your Personal Information with third parties as follows:

* **Service Providers**: Your Personal Information may be shared with or collected by third party service providers who provide us with services, including but not limited to data hosting or processing, credit card processing or processing and fulfilling purchases. We may also avail services from Twilio for sending emails, Amazon Webservices for cloud infrastructure services, Webflow for website related services and Smartproxy for cookie consent products. We require these providers to exercise reasonable care to protect your Personal Information and restrict the use of your Personal Information to the purposes for which it was provided to them.
* **Merger or Acquisition:** We may transfer your Personal Information if we are acquired by another entity, or if we merge with another company or transfer a part of our business, including the Website, to a third party. Any such third party or resultant entity that receives your Personal Information shall have the right to continue to use your Personal Information in line with the purposes set out herein. In the event of such a sale or transfer, we may notify you.
* **Aggregate Information:** We may share your Personal Information with affiliated or non-affiliated third parties on an anonymous, aggregate basis. While this information will not identify you personally, in some instances these third parties may be able to combine this aggregate information with other data they have about you, or that they receive from third parties, in a manner that allows them to identify you personally.
* **Legal and Regulatory Authorities: We may disclose your Personal Information in order to comply with our legal obligations/ court orders/ requests by Govt. authorities.**

### 6\. **How long do we store your Personal Information?**  

We will retain your Personal Information as long as it is required to be retained for the purpose of provision of the Offerings and to comply with our legal obligations. Subject to this section, we will delete your Personal Information upon reasonable written request for the same. Please note, however, that there might be latency in deleting Personal Information from our servers. For more information on where and how long your Personal Information is stored, please contact vaibhav@privado.ai. Where your Personal Information is processed by us on the basis of your consent we will delete or anonymise your data if you withdraw your consent.

### 7\. **Our security measures**

Your Personal Information is stored on servers located in the EEA. We have implemented encryption mechanism and provide appropriate firewalls and protections. There may be data pilferage due to unauthorized hacking, virus attacks, technical issues, which may be due to external factors not in our control and we will take necessary measures to mitigate any such adverse events.

We maintain a detailed disclosure regarding our security and compliance measures available on our Website at [www.privado.ai/security-compliance](https://www.privado.ai/security-compliance)

### **8\. Indian Individual’s Rights**

You have the right to access Personal Information in our possession, right to have us rectify or modify any such Personal Information, right to have us erase/delete your Personal Information, right to restrict us from processing such Personal Information, right to object to our use of Personal Information, withdraw consent at any time where we are relying on consent to process  Personal Information. Depending on the nature of the request, we may ask you to complete a Personal Information request form or seek certain details to verify the request. All requests for Personal Information will be handled within a reasonable period of time. If you would like to exercise ANY of these rights, please contact vaibhav@privado.ai.

### 9\. **Information for EU/EEA visitors**

* **Applicability of GDPR:** Residents of the European Union (“**EU**”) and United Kingdom (“**UK**”) should note that this Privacy Policy has been updated in accordance with the requirements of the EU General Data Protection Regulation (the “**GDPR**”) and the UK GDPR, the United Kingdom Data Protection Act 2018, the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations, and any regulation superseding any of the foregoing (“**UK Privacy Laws**”). As per the provisions of the GDPR and UK Privacy Laws we shall be considered the Controllers of the Personal information collected as a result of your use/access of the Website.
* **Legal Basis (for EU residents and UK residents):** We will not process your Personal Information without a lawful basis to do so. We will process your Personal Information only on the legal bases of consent provided that such interests are not overridden by your privacy rights and interests.
* **Transfer of Your Personal Information Across Borders:** There may be instances when the processing of your Personal Information will involve a transfer of Personal Information outside the EU and UK. Whenever we transfer your Personal Information, we ensure a similar degree of protection is afforded to it by ensuring that any such international transfers are made subject to appropriate or suitable safeguards as required by GDPR and UK Privacy Laws. We ensure that such transfers are governed through the adequate Standard Contractual Clauses (SCC). If you have questions, please contact us as at vaibhav@privado.ai
* **Your Rights:** You have the right to request us to let you know what Personal Information belonging to you do we hold in our possession, right to have us rectify or modify any such Personal Information, right to have us erase/delete your Personal Information, right to restrict us from processing such Personal Information, right to object to our use of your Personal Information. If you would like to exercise ANY of these rights, please contact vaibhav@privado.aiWhenever we rely on your consent to process your Personal Information, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time by contacting us atvaibhav@privado.ai. If you are a resident of the EU and UK, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a data protection authority/supervisory authority of your region.  
* UK residents have the right to make a complaint at any time to the Information Commissioner’s Office (“**ICO**”), the UK supervisory authority for data protection issues (www.ico.org.uk). We would, however, appreciate the chance to deal with your concerns before you approach the ICO so please contact us in the first instance. We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity or also contact you for further information in relation to your request. If you would like to exercise ANY of these rights, please contact vaibhav@privado.ai .
* **Governing Laws: For any EU and UK residents, this Privacy Statement shall be governed respectively by the provisions of the GDPR and UK Privacy Laws.**

### 9\. **California resident rights**

**If you are a California resident, you have the rights as mentioned below;**

* **Access:** You have the right to request certain information about our collection and use of your Personal Data over the past 12 months. If we have disclosed your Personal Information for a business purpose over the past 12 months, we will identify the categories of Personal Data shared with each category of third-party recipient. If we have sold your Personal Information over the past 12 months, we will identify the categories of Personal Information purchased by each category of third-party recipient.
* **Deletion_:_** You have the right to request that we delete the Personal Information that we have collected from you.
* **Right to know:** You have the right to know the categories of Personal Information, categories of sources, and/or categories of third parties related to the processing of your Personal Information.
* **Right to Opt-Out of sale or sharing of Personal Information:** You have a right to opt out of any data sharing or sale of data related to your Personal Information.
* **Right to correct:** You have a right to correct any incorrect data that may be recorded with us.
* While we do not collect any sensitive Personal Information, you have a right to limit use and disclosure of sensitive personal information.
* **Right not to be subjected to fully automated decision making:** If any fully automated decision is taking place, you have a right to object to such decision making.

**Exercising Your Rights:** To exercise the rights described above, you must send us a request that (1) provides sufficient information to allow us to verify that you are the person about whom we have collected Personal Information and (2) describes your request in sufficient detail to allow us to understand, evaluate, and respond to it. Each request that meets both of these criteria will be considered a “Valid Request.” We may not respond to requests that do not meet these criteria. We will only use Personal Information provided in a Valid Request to verify you and complete your request. You do not need an account to submit a Valid Request. We will respond to your Valid Request within 45 days of receipt. We will not charge you with any fees for making a Valid Request unless your Valid Request(s) is excessive, repetitive, or manifestly unfounded. If we determine that your Valid Request warrants any fees, we will notify you of the fees and explain that decision before completing your request. You may submit your Valid Request at vaibhav@privado.ai.

**No Discrimination:** We will not discriminate against you for exercising your rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act (the “**CCPA**”). We will not deny you our Offerings, charge you different prices or rates, or provide you a lower quality of our Offerings if you exercise your rights under the CCPA.

**Authorized agents.** You may also authorize an agent (an “Authorized Agent”) to exercise your rights on your behalf. To do this, you must provide your Authorized Agent with written permission to do, and we may request a copy of this written permission from your Authorized Agent when they make a request to exercise your rights on your behalf.

### 11\. **Links to other websites**

Our Website may contain links to other websites/applications of your interest. Please note that we do not have any control over such other websites/applications, and you will be accessing these websites/applications at your own risk. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such websites/applications and those are not governed by this Privacy Policy. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy policies applicable to such websites/applications.

### 12\. **Choice and Opt-Out**

We may send you communications including but not limited to (a) notices about your use of our Website and Offerings, including those concerning violations of use, (b) updates, (c) promotional information regarding our Offerings, and (d) newsletters. You may opt out of receiving promotional emails and newsletters from us by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in those emails. Alternatively, you can opt out, at any time, by emailing vaibhav@privado.aiwith your specific request.

### 13\. **Limitation of liability**

To the extent permissible under the law, we shall not be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequential or exemplary damages, including but not limited to, damages for loss of profits, goodwill, data, information, or other intangible losses (even if we have been advised of the possibility of such damages), arising out of this Privacy Policy.

### 14\. **Governing laws**

This Privacy Policy shall be construed and governed by the laws of Delaware and the courts of Delaware shall have an exclusive jurisdiction to adjudicate any subject matter under this Privacy Policy.

### 15\. **Changes to this privacy policy**

Please revisit this page periodically to stay aware of any changes to this Privacy Policy, which we may update from time to time. If we modify this Privacy Policy, we will make it available through the Website and indicate the date of the latest revision. In the event that the modifications materially alter your rights or obligations hereunder, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you of the change through our Website.

This Privacy Policy was last modified on September 1, 2023.

### 16\. **Contact us**

If you have any questions or concerns or grievances regarding this Privacy Policy or wish to withdraw your consent in relation to the processing of your Personal Information, you can contact  our appointed grievance redressal officer Vaibhav Antil via the following ways:

* Email us at vaibhav@privado.ai

Postal Address: Privado Inc., 8 The Green Suite, #11305, Dover, DE, 19901, United States.

Contact Us
----------

For any questions or concerns, you can contact us in one of the following ways.  
  
Email us at [security@privado.ai](mailto:security@privado.ai)

Privado syncs privacy compliance with software development by providing full data visibility and continuous privacy governance.

Product

SolutionS

Free Tools

Resources

COMPANY

Support

© 2024 Privado Inc.

Cookie Settings
